{
    "subject": "resource/Chris_Penn",
    "predicate": "property/relatives",
    "object": "resource/Sean_Penn",
    "human_readable": "Chris Penn is related to Sean Penn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9842812418937683,
            "question": "Are Chris Penn and Sean Penn related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9841862320899963,
            "question": "Who are Chris Penn and Sean Penn related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9675689339637756,
            "question": "Is Chris Penn a family member of Sean Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9656628370285034,
            "question": "Is there a familial relationship between Chris Penn and Sean Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9491441249847412,
            "question": "Are Chris Penn and Sean Penn brothers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9360736608505249,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Chris Penn and Sean Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.840063750743866,
            "question": "How are Chris Penn and Sean Penn connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8314213156700134,
            "question": "What is the connection between the actors Chris Penn and Sean Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8294938206672668,
            "question": "What is the nature of the connection between Chris Penn and Sean Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8104951977729797,
            "question": "Do Chris Penn and Sean Penn share any familial ties?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Penn is related to Sean Penn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6446_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nature of the connection between Chris Penn and Sean Penn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6446_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the connection between the actors Chris Penn and Sean Penn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6446_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How are Chris Penn and Sean Penn connected?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6446_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6446_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Chris Penn is the brother of actor Sean Penn, which confirms the relationship stated in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}